Alright, let's go on.
We'll be right back.
Secret Bond! Iceberg and Frankie!
Storm's coming, huh?
Better finish this up before the wind gets even worse.
What's he doing?
Give it back!
We need the money to fix the berry.
Her scars are deep.
That's our money!
It's to heal her wounds, understand me?
You can't have it!
Give it back to me right now!
Oh, I see now.
That must be the ship he needed the money to have repaired he was talking about.
What a disaster.
Yeah, even if we didn't come here to nab him, Aqualaguna would still wash him away.
Talk about bad luck.
Okay.
I had just enough lumber to patch up the rough spot, so it should hold even if it's not pretty.
You're wasting your time, pal.
Who's there?
Come on, you're kidding me, right?
Or did we beat you so bad you already forgot who I am?
Pull it together, man.
Oh, no!
Anybody but him!
What do you want?
Leave me alone, you bastard!
Now, now.
Let's all calm down.
As long as you play it cool, I won't have to hurt you.
Even I'm not crazy enough to fight a guy in the middle of this storm.
But if we don't want to sink, it looks like I'll have to take that ship of yours hostage as well.
What are you talking about?
Well, I got a score to settle with Straw Hat, you see.
So I came here to kidnap you.
I used the backside.
They're fine.
I hope you're proud of yourself beating those poor shipwrights!
You're so strong, Zoro!
Whatever.
Might as well go ahead.
Zoro, this way!
Got it!
No!
Over here!
We're leading the way for you, stupid!
How can you get lost already?
Oh, here.
Zoro's gone!
I think we lost it forever!
We're doing this on purpose!
Zoro, where did you go?!
Zoro!
See?
I can do that stuff!
Because I'm rubber!
OK.
That's good!
Now do that with the rest of your body.
Sure!
Just give me a sec!
Easy, cause I'm rubber!
Alright, good, now help me!
No prob!
You're going to pay, you masked bastards!
It's true, we've been undercover for the last five years.
Ah, but don't worry, we took our jobs as shipwrights very seriously.
I understand how shocked you must be.
However, we can't devote any more time to this matter.
We will achieve our goal by any means necessary.
So if you're thinking about resisting for the sake of being difficult, I suggest you reconsider.
For your own good as well as ours.
I assume you're already familiar with CypherPol.
It's the government's supreme intelligence agency with eight branches.
Their worldwide bases are referred to as CP1 through CP8.
Together, they serve as the government's eyes and ears in every corner of the globe.
Of course I know.
But how do all of you fit into that picture?
Good question.
As the ninth CypherPol unit, we officially do not exist.
And by virtue of that, we possess a certain privilege that the other branches lack.
One that necessitates a degree of secrecy.
A privilege?
That's right.
Consider it a blade we wield in the name of justice.
If a citizen is uncooperative towards the government, we may execute them.
You fools.
You can't use justice as an excuse for murder.
Recently, the government has been forced to change its way of thinking.
For example, rather than fearing Pluton's revival, they have decided to awaken it.
To use the ancient weapon as a force of justice that can bring an end to the great pirate era.
And now, for some reason, you want to stand in their way.
It's almost as if you have no sympathy for all of the people constantly being victimized by pirates.
You should reconsider where your loyalties lie.
Don't kid yourself.
If the weapon is restored, the world is going to fight over its power.
It will only breed more destruction.
Are you saying you don't trust the government, Mr. Iceberg?
That would be a shame.
Not at all.
It's human nature that I don't trust.
Luchi.
Show some respect.
Remember, you're not my boss anymore.
Kaku, check his pulse.
Excuse me.
Here's the situation.
A while ago, we came up with a bit of a hypothesis about the blueprints.
You needn't worry.
Although we could torture you, we have more effective means of extracting the truth.
All you have to do is lie there and listen to our hypothesis without saying a word.
Even if your mouth won't cooperate, your pulse will tell us the truth.
The wind is out to get you.
Better be careful.
Hey!
Hey, Granny!
Are we going back?
The storm's coming!
Oh, yeah?
Seems like a perfect time for a stroll around town, if you ask me.
Gives me a little time to sober up.
Oh?
Then why aren't you still drinking, Granny?
You can't sober up and booze it up at the same time, can you?
Sure I can.
I haven't been drinking all my life for nothing.
Huh?
All your life?
That's not true!
It hasn't been all my life.
It's only been eight years.
Now that we're all comfortable, let me explain the thought process leading to our hypothesis.
First of all, the way that you allowed us to retrieve the fake blueprints is highly suspicious.
After you decided that the culprits were related to the government, you intentionally revealed the location of the fakes, presumably in the hopes of fooling us.
However, what if your assumption was wrong and the culprit's intention was to kill you rather than to retrieve the blueprints?
In that case, the fakes would be useless, the real blueprints would be lost, and the will of the original shipwrights would not be passed on.
Surely you considered that possibility.
I know you're no fool.
And yet, despite creating a decoy, you've seemingly made no attempt to pass off the actual blueprints tonight.
That must mean you've already entrusted them to someone.
We still don't know where they are, but we can assume that you don't have them with you anymore.
That's our hypothesis.
Uh-uh.
No squirming.
This is still just a theory.
I admit, we haven't found any decisive evidence.
And despite the fact that we've kept you under surveillance for the past five years, we've never seen you do anything suspicious.
Assuming you did entrust the blueprints to someone, they would have to be an accomplished shipwright to make any sense out of them.
Now, if we add that to our theory, things start to get interesting.
For example, let's take a closer look at the fake blueprints that you left us.
Here at the bottom, you can see the signatures of three different shipwrights.
Tom, Iceberg, and Cuddy Flan.
And the company name, Tom's Workers.
You probably thought that this detail wouldn't mean anything to whoever took the bait, but you had no idea your enemies were so close.
That was a grave miscalculation on your part.
If the person who broke in had been an outsider, once they found out that the blueprints had nothing to do with Pluton, they would probably have thrown them away.
However, since we've been shipwrights ourselves for the past five years, the names of the designers are very interesting.
There's a visitor, sir, to see you.
Although many people know of the legendary shipwright Tom, the details of his actual company are shrouded in mystery.
It's believed to have existed on this island, but there's no roster or register to be found.
It was no easy task finding out that you were one of Tom's apprentices.
What few reports we have indicate that he taught only two shipwrights, and a government official verified that one of them died in an accident eight years ago.
Real shame.
I know Cuddy Flam was a bit of a loose cannon, but I sure hate to see him go.
It struck a chord, I thought to myself. Now, where have I heard that name before?
He said he's a friend from years back. Do you know anyone named Cuddy Flam?
It was about four years ago, shortly after we started our undercover operation.
He was a man who has passed through Galilaw's gates many times since, but only once did he ever use that name.
I remember it clearly.
So do I.
Shall I show him in, sir?
No. Turn him away.
In other words, Tom's second apprentice, Cuddy Flam, is still alive.
And living in this town, no less.
But now he goes by Frank.
And what's with all the secrecy? Something going on?
Hey, what are these? The blueprints for that old battleship?
Don't call yourself Cuddy Flam anymore.
It's only a matter of time before the government targets me.
I want you to take these and leave this island, Frankie.
Seems pretty obvious now, huh?
I can't believe it took us all these years to figure out the connection.
Our searches on him turned up nothing.
I must admit that his true identity was a well-hidden secret.
And because he's an oaf and a ship dismantler, we never really gave him much thought.
It's ironic, really.
What's the price?
How dare you?
گ
疲れ果てた武器の中でも変わらないもの探すコンバスで いつまでも持っていれるから
いつか辿り着く夢の終わりに できるだけこのままで大人に 見上げた果てしないこの大空に 永遠に 永遠に
幼き頃の夢物語 忘られち記憶の糸辿り 未だ胸を焦がす残り火を消してしまわないように
乱れた羽渡るこの空に 仲間と共に想いを託し 移り変わる時代を越え 永遠に 永遠に
an ovalみたいなものに
ラグだったけど 相手の群集を反映して 車のための部分を見つけたみたい
・別に 良いです
はい 微見にしましできれません そこまで共に臨成し
もう驚